{
    "id": "063763c7491547fb89de703b4b450bc1",
    "title": "Sentence correction worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "346d7dc3c6b044f684ebc42ce3e334d2",
            "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "My sister and I enjoy ...................... in the sea.",
                    "description": "After enjoy, we use an -ing form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "to swim",
                        "swimming"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I think you have forgotten .......................... your homework.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to do",
                        "doing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He works hard ....................... a living.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "earning",
                        "to earn"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Rani studies .......................... good marks.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "scoring",
                        "to score"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The traveler requested the passer-by ......................... him a hand.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "lending",
                        "to lend"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Mother did not let me ......................... out with my friends.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go",
                        "going",
                        "to go"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He didnâ€™t let me ............................ his room.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to enter",
                        "enter",
                        "entering"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The children are busy .......................... their project.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "doing",
                        "do",
                        "to do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am looking forward ........................... you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "seeing",
                        "to seeing",
                        "to see"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I meant ........................... the letter, but I forgot.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to be posting",
                        "to have posted",
                        "posting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}